shoespie.com 2019-01-26

# Privacy & Security Policy – shoesPie.com

(1)Collection of Personal Data

In order to provide you with the personalized recommended products, efficient customer service, and timely news notification, we record some information you’ve given previously from your visit to our site and your registration and browsing of our site. 

Including your name, e-mail address, gender, your account settings, IP, fingerprint data, device information, your billing and shipping address information, phone number, address, credit card information, language preference, merchandise category preferences.

At Shoespie.com, we respect and take the protection for your personal information very seriously. We ensure that your privacy is protected when using our services. Once we receive your data transmission, we have technical and organizational measures in place to help protect your data from loss, manipulation, unauthorized access, etc. We continually adapt our security measures in line with technological progress and developments. We protect your data using encryption using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL is a function that encrypts all information sent between buyer and seller, including card information, so that card details cannot be read by external parties.

(2)Use of Personal Data

We collect Personal Information that you provide to us voluntarily and process it for the following purposes:

To create your personal account at Shoespie.com

To complete transactions with you;

To be able to contact you in the event of any problem with the delivery of your items;

To communicate with you the latest market trend and enable you to participate in promotions if you have ever subscribed;

To know your needs and preferences and recommend personalized products;

To develop, enhance, market and provide products and services to meet your needs;

To process exchanges or product returns;

To improve our services and respond to requests or complaints.

(3)The Content & Frequency of our communication with you

·For automatically triggered email and SMS notifications

We may send you a confirmation email or a SMS verification after you register with Shoespie as well as service-related notifications as necessary. 

For example: 

Your order confirmation email;

Your address change confirmation email;

Your payment confirmation email;

Your order delivery notice;

Your package logistics method changing notification;

The above list are closely related to your order. We strongly recommend that you do not unsubscribe. If you insist on deleting your account information, the above email will not be received again.

The frequency of these notifications is closely related to your interaction on our website. We cannot promise a certain amount of delivery.

How to delete my account: 

Please refer to (7)Right to Opt-out.

·For manually group email or SMS notifications

We will send group email newsletter and SMS newsletter notifications after we received your subscription request. The content of such notification contains:

Special offers for subscribers only;

New products updated;

Website promotion and coupon;

Products personalized recommendation;

Shopping and wearing, maintenance tips;

Updates of service policy.

You may receive above notifications 2-5 time per week in average. You can unsubscribe at any time.

How to unsubscribe: 

Please refer to (7)Right to Opt-out.

(4)Cookies

Cookie is a small text file that is saved to and during subsequent visits, retrieved from, your computer or mobile device. Shoespie uses cookies to enhance and simplify your visit. We do not use cookies to disclose information to third parties. There are also third-party cookies on our Sites, which we use to collect statistics in aggregate form in analysis tools such as Google Analytics. Some of these cookies may track your behavior across multiple websites. There are two types of cookies persistent and temporary (session cookies). 

Persistent cookies are stored as a file on your computer or mobile device for a time period no longer than 24 months. 

Session cookies are stored temporarily and disappear when you close your browser. We use persistent cookies to store your shipping country and shopping bag unless you log in. We use session cookies when to check whether you are logged in or not. 

You can easily erase cookies from your computer or mobile device using your browser. For instructions on how to handle and delete cookies please look under "Help" in your browser. You can choose to disable cookies, or to receive a notification each time a new cookie is sent to your computer or mobile device. However, please note that if you choose to disable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of all features such as:

Speed up navigation 

Track site usage

Recognize users and user access privileges 

Enable selection and purchase products on this Site record your browsing activity and purchases

Web Beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the Sites and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages.

(5)Children’s Privacy

If you are under 16 years old please use Shoespie.com only given or authorized by the holder of parental responsibility over the child. 

Shoespie do not collect, use, or transfer data to third parties with any data from children under 13. We will immediately delete the data when we learn that we have collected the personal data of a child under 13. If you find any child under 13 years old was registered on our site, please contact us to delete.

Email:service@shoespie.com

Telephone:+86-29-68968082

(6) Processing of information

You agreed to clearly and fully understand, for the sole purpose that providing you with the personalized recommended products, efficient customer service, and timely news notification, we shall have the right to your personal data or data set for processing, including but not limited to the following any one or a series of operations, such as collecting, recording, organization, construction, storage, adaptive or modify, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure, dissemination or other use of, arrangement, combination, limit, delete, or destroyed, whether or not the operation using automated means.

(7)Right to Opt-out

Delete my account

Shoespie is committed to providing you with continuous, high quality products and services. But if you want to delete all your data information on our website, we respect your choice and shall fully cooperate. Please contact Shoespie customer service and they will reply you within 48 hours. All your information will be completely deleted from the server of Shoespie.

Shortly afterwards, you can submit delete account request through our web page. This is currently under development. Before this, you can contact customer service to help to delete.

No more emails or messages

If you no longer wish to receive the Company's promotional communications, you may opt-out by  unsubscribe from these communications at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained at the bottom of each email. You can unsubscribe from SMS by e-mailing our customer service at service@shoespie.com.

Our Company Name : Tidebuy International Limited Poland Branch office

Address: Ul.Aleja Krakowska 165,lok.C13/C14 Lazy,05-552 Jablonowo,Poland

Tel:+48 739660518(not for customer service)

Our Company Name :Tidebuy LLC

Address: 2075 E.REDONDO BEACH BLVD,GARDENA ,CA,UNITED STATES
